{
    "subject": "resource/Broken_Crayon_Games",
    "predicate": "ontology/industry",
    "object": "resource/Video_game_industry",
    "human_readable": "Broken Crayon Games operates in the video game industry.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9691658020019531,
            "question": "What industry does Broken Crayon Games operate in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9485505223274231,
            "question": "Is Broken Crayon Games involved in the film industry?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.763446569442749,
            "question": "Are there any other companies similar to Broken Crayon Games?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7546160221099854,
            "question": "What are some examples of games made by Broken Crayon Games?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7508093118667603,
            "question": "What type of products does Broken Crayon Games create?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7475999593734741,
            "question": "Where is Broken Crayon Games headquartered?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7443492412567139,
            "question": "Does Broken Crayon Games make toys?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7240633368492126,
            "question": "Who are some of the key people working at Broken Crayon Games?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7076999545097351,
            "question": "Does Broken Crayon Games develop games for mobile devices?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.669572651386261,
            "question": "What makes Broken Crayon Games stand out from other game developers?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Broken Crayon Games operates in the video game industry.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5272_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does Broken Crayon Games develop games for mobile devices?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5272_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who are some of the key people working at Broken Crayon Games?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5272_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does Broken Crayon Games make toys?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5272_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5272_120.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5272_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5272_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5272_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5272_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5272_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5272_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5272_72.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5272_87.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5272_90.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON response:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents mention \"Broken Crayon Games\" as one of the development studios located in Pennsylvania, which suggests that Broken Crayon Games operates in the video game industry."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\"output\": \"yes\"}\n```\n\nExplanation:\nThe document states that Pennsylvania has several development studios, including Schell Games, Broken Crayon Games, and Space Whale Studios. This information supports that \"Broken Crayon Games\" operates in the video game industry."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}